export const quizPack = [
  {
    question: `In 1768, Captain James Cook set out to explore which ocean?`,
    A: `Pacific Ocean`,
    B: `Atlantic Ocean`,
    C: `Indian Ocean`,
    D: `Arctic Ocean`,
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    question: `What is actually electricity?`,
    A: `A flow of water`,
    B: `A flow of air`,
    C: `A flow of electrons`,
    D: `A flow of atoms`,
    answer: 'C'
  },
  {
    question: `Which of the following is not an international organisation?`,
    A: `FIFA`,
    B: `NATO`,
    C: `ASEAN`,
    D: `FBI`,
    answer: 'D'
  },
  {
    question: `Which of the following disorders is the fear of being alone?`,
    A: `Agoraphobia`,
    B: `Aerophobia`,
    C: `Acrophobia`,
    D: `Arachnophobia`,
    answer: 'A'
  },
  {
    question: `Which of the following is a song by the German heavy metal band “Scorpions”?`,
    A: `Stairway to Heaven`,
    B: `Wind of Change`,
    C: `Don’t Stop Me Now`,
    D: `Hey Jude`,
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    question: `What is the speed of sound?`,
    A: `120 km/h`,
    B: `1,200 km/h`,
    C: `400 km/h`,
    D: `700 km/h`,
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    question: `Which is the easiest way to tell the age of many trees?`,
    A: `To measure the width of the tree`,
    B: `To count the rings on the trunk`,
    C: `To count the number of leaves`,
    D: `To measure the height of the tree`,
    answer: 'B'
  },
  {
    question: `What do we call a newly hatched butterfly?`,
    A: `A moth`,
    B: `A butter`,
    C: `A caterpillar`,
    D: `A chrysalis`,
    answer: 'C'
  },
  {
    question: `In total, how many novels were written by the Bronte sisters?`,
    A: `4`,
    B: `5`,
    C: `6`,
    D: `7`,
    answer: 'D'
  },
  {
    question: `Which did Viking people use as money?`,
    A: `Rune stones`,
    B: `Jewellery`,
    C: `Seal skins`,
    D: `Wool`,
    answer: 'B'
  },
]